

## **UMBERTO SEMELEER**

USER INTERACTION GRADUTION INTERNSHIP • OOST-, WEST- EN MIDDELBEERS, 5091RN,, NETHERLAND • +31639354983

#### • DETAILS •

Esdoorn 18
Oost-, West- en Middelbeers,
5091RN,
Netherland
+31639354983

#### Umberto.a.semeleer@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 18-11-1994

Aruba

Nationality Dutch

Driving license

В

## • LINKS •

<u>Instagram</u>

<u>Linkedln</u>

#### • RELEVANT SKILLS •

Ability to work independently and in a team.

Hands-on Learning"

Adaptability

Problem solving mindset

## LANGUAGES

English

Dutch

Spanish

Papiamento

## HOBBIES

Cooking
cycling
3D printing
Woodwork with laser cutting
Planting/gardening

#### PROFILE

Fourth year at Fontys ICT studying Advanced Media Design and a specialaztion in Game Design & Technology with previous experience in electrical installations and cooling systems. Very social and can communicate in a calm and professional manner. Works very well independently but is also a strong and diverse team member. Creative problem solver who likes to take on new challenges

#### EDUCATION

MAVO (biology, physics, chemistry) , Juliana School , Aruba September 2012 — June 2017

MBO niveau 4 Electrotechniek, EPI Aruba, Aruba

September 2013 — June 2017

Specialize in Electrical installation and refrigeration systems.

Electrical Engineering (1 year ), Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Eindhoven September 2019 — February 2020

Bachelor ICT & Media Design/specialization Game Design & technology, Fontys University of Applied Sciences, Eindhoven

February 2020 — Present

**Semester 1:** During my orientation phase, I gained foundational knowledge in the ICT-related fields of Business, Infrastructure, Media Design, Software Engineering, and Technology.

**Semester 2:** Media Design, I gained insights into Media Production, User-Centered Design, and Web Development. During this time, I had the opportunity to revamp an e-commerce website, refining its user interface, navigation, and overall design.

**Semester 3:** Media Design, I learned about Concept and Interaction Design, Interactive Media Product, and Stakeholder Communication. I designed and built a loyalty program for client "Team Liquid," using full stack development techniques.

Semester 4: Specialization in Game Design & Technology, delved into Game Design, Game Technology, and Applied Game Aesthetics. This led to hands-on experience in developing a first-person shooter and platformer game using Unity and VR technology. Additionally, I participated in a team to create an educational multiplayer game for primary schoolers for client Winclove Probiotics B.V.

Semester 5: Media Design internship (Details in Work Experience page 2).

Semester 6: Completed the minor embrace tec which focuses on product development gaining skills in 3D printing, laser cutting, woodworking, CNC milling, and electronics. Worked with diverse clients including Novadic-Kentron and Regionale Opvang Zwerfdieren Eindhoven.

**Semester 7:** Advanced Media Desig. *In process.* Focus Areas: Music in education, typography and design, and humanizing objects. **Industry Projects:** Developed a referral program for Bierens Group and an experience center for Simac.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Part time Bike Courier/shelf stocker at Flink, Eindhoven

November 2024 — Present

Delivering customer order with an electric bike, assist in back-of-house tasks when needed, help organize and restock shelves according to FIFO. Working here is teaching me to pay close attention to important details, manage my time more efficiently and follow the correct procedures. I enjoy the many diverse interactions I get with customers.

## UX&UI Design & front end developer internship at Simptel B.V., Eindhoven

February 2023 — August 2023

During my internship, I helped develop a white-label platform for VoIP services by focusing on front-end design while coordinating with back-end developers. Gained experience using Agile Scrum methodology for efficient task management, which facilitated timely project delivery and enhanced collaboration between team members. I gained a lot of valuable experience by working with an international team with offices across the Netherlands and India. Communication was done both remotely and in person and this taught me to work effectively with different cultures and locations.

#### Independent contractor electrician, Aruba

August 2017 — June 2019

I have worked on several housing projects and joined a start-up project manufacturing Mini-Houses where I was responsible for designing and installing electrical systems based on client preferences. By collaborating with other professional contractors and the client I ensured client satisfaction. I gained valuable experience in design, construction, teamwork, and client service and use this knowledge in my current studies.

## Electrician at Rotech Technical Services, Aruba, Aruba

July 2017 — January 2018

I was assigned to various projects in Aruba's High-rise and Low-rise Hotel area where I undertook a range of responsibilities including electrical demolition and installation. I also conducted infrared inspections of the electrical control panels to ensure and uphold the safety and efficiency standards. Problem-solving and quick-thinking skills were crucial to have in order to diagnose and fix any electrical malfunction. I often had to collaborate with fellow technicians.

## Part time Koelmonteur at Aruba Climate Control, Aruba

June 2016 — December 2016

I worked in teams max of 3 conducting regular walk-throughs with our clients on-site. The job involved installing refrigeration and air conditioning systems, as well as maintaining and repairing these installations.

# Part time Electrician assistant at High Technology Sales & Services (Hitess) NV, Aruba, Aruba

July 2015 — November 2015

I was responsible for assembling large electrical control panels and designing electrical panel maps using AutoCAD. Additionally, I assembled control panels, switching, and distribution equipment for various applications, including industry, residential, and commercial buildings.